dresstokillmagazine.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Fashion Magazine - Dress To Kill

Your use of any part of the [**Dress to Kill**](http://dresstokillmagazine.com/denis-gagnon-dream-dress-kill-magazine/ "Denis Gagnon & the Dream that is Dress to Kill magazine! #GalleryDTK") [**Website**](http://dresstokillmagazine.com/aritzia/ "Aritzia") will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This policy can change without prior notice.

THE TYPE OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:  
This site does not collect any information without your consent. Any personal information you submit i.e. to subscribe to our magazine, to be on our mailing [**list**](http://dresstokillmagazine.com/category/list/ "list"), surveys and contests will not be transferred to a third party without prior consent.  
We may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including the type of browser you use, the operating system you are running, the Website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet and does not refer to your exact location or civic address.

HOW WE WILL USE THE INFORMATION:  
This site will mainly gather information for subscriptions and your mailing address for our newsletter. We might also ask you to fill mini-surveys to be used to compile statistics that will help us draw a clear portrait of our readership. We could also contact you via e-mail with offers of interest by our advertisers or partners. You can decide at any time to be removed from the list, all you have to do is contact us with a request.  
The information we gather might be viewed by a service provider, IT person, or anyone that will help us manage the Website and the database. This person or organization will be granted access under a confidentiality agreement.

INFORMATION SECURITY  
We will safeguard all personal data collected by this Website. However we cannot guarantee infallibility of our security systems. Any time you submit information to us, you are agreeing to this possible risk.

USE OF WEBSITE BY MINORS  
This Website is not intended for use by children. Since we cannot control who gains access to our Website, it is the responsibility of the parent(s) or legal guardian to monitor their activities.
